Ah.
Man, it's freezing in here.
I mean, how long are they
gonna go at it today?
I haven't eaten anything
since this morning.
I'm starving.
What should I eat when I get home?
Oh, look, I told you, bigger is better.
If we're gonna make it fight,
heavier is the best choice.
Well, then go find it and call back later.
Huh?
No guard.
Need to go somewhere?
Hell of a time to take a bathroom break.
Hey, look at this! Huh?
You think he eats fish sausage?
Wait a minute.
That thing was in the
tournament, wasn't it?
Oh, you got a little panda.
Hey, Joe, fish pandas don't
eat meat, they eat bamboo.
Well, this panda eats fish sausage.
No cameras on the emergency stairs.
Yo!
You sure about this?
It's a risky plan!
It could cause you trouble later on!
It's fine!
We just need to secure
the area by the door.
Oh no! It's Kirara!
What are they doing?
Away from Hakari!
It's Panda, and that spiky-haired kid?
If panda helped him sneak in here,
that means he's with jujutsu high?
which means Yui is with Jujutsu High too.
And then that means Kin is in danger.
Look, boss, I need to tell you something.
Demon dog, totality!
Pushy girl!
My demon dog was thrown back?
No.
Judging from what Panda said, it
couldn't get close enough to them.
There.
Panda and the other two are marked.
The monitor room.
Kiroro's planning on
heading back to Hakari.
Wait, Kimara!
We're not your enemies!
We just want to ask Akari for a favor!
I don't believe that!
I'm disappointed in you, Panda!
This is pathetic!
I can't even get close to
you while walking or running!
Suguru and I can't get
close to us, either.
Tushikuro!
It's more than just being
able to approach them.
I can't separate from Demon Dog, either.
What kind of a curse technique is this?
Listen! Save it, kid!
My passion has gone cold!
All right, let's hold
your heart, let it be.
Let's get it right,
let's try and let it be.
Let's try again, let's see?
Not yet capable of me.
Expo the picture, the truth is!
I'm sorry, it's not fair to forgive.
Don't let this beat me!
My wird's got a feeling.
No high tension.
Yerolette. Nashi jah.
Oto na Shoko wa na me nai.
Love me love me.
Kara sa bakari de.
Love me happy.
Sambu uka te.
Love me love me.
Aizou mami rete.
Koko o tsula basute. Yeah!
Aizou Aizou.
Take out the.
Psycho joy.
Yo Iizu dente.
Da ma shi da ma shi de ii no.
Da i Show nante ki ni shi nai yo.
Aizou Aizou ni mo Code.
We're at a stalemate. Perfect.
Hirata!
We're not currently with Jujutsu High.
You know what Tokyo's
like right now, don't you?
The barriers that sprung up in
each region are related as well.
It was an unprecedented attack!
Of jujutsu terrorism
we need hikari's help.
Well, you're the ones who
excluded us in the first place.
You reap what you sow.
I told you we're not with jujutsu high.
What happened between
you and the higher ups?
They fought with the conservatives.
Of course, their idea of conservative?
and goes beyond just their
policy toward the regulations.
They have set ideas of what
and what not jujutsu should be.
Kugisaki's technique is a good example.
That's the kind of classic
jujutsu the conservatives prefer.
Not stuff like the cursed videos
that were popular a while back.
As time goes on, even jujutsu
incorporates more new technologies.
But some of those new techniques are
bound to make the conservatives fussing.
Kim's technique is a
perfect example of that.
That's why those stupid higher-ups lost.
Here's an idea.
Why don't you have Satoru Gojo save
your asses for you like always?
If you have him, why do
you need us so badly, huh?
The answer is you're
lying about needing us,
which means you're here
for some other reason,
right?
Satoru Gojo has been sealed away.
It's the reason we lost.
Oh no they don't believe us?
Well I can understand that but this
person is the one closest to Hakari.
Rabbit escape bunny rabbits?
I can just convince them negotiations
with the Car will go more smoothly.
Hey, Crux.
God, Crux.
That's a lot of bunnies.
What's he up to?
My technique marks cursed energy,
so it treats sorcerers and their
shikigamis the exact same thing.
At this rate, the bunnies will be
drawn to him like that dog he was,
and he'll be crushed under his
own shikigami until he suffocates.
Panda, what happened?
Tell me about Rabbit Escape.
They were almost as cute as I am.
I don't mean how they looked.
What were they able to
approach and not approach?
No.
They were able to get up to that
second floor with no problem.
But they couldn't get
near Kirava or the door.
Panda, do you have anything
written on your body?
A star and a name somewhere.
Oh, Imai!
I should have one too.
Imai! There!
It's actually mine!
Just like on the rabbits.
It's probably on totality too.
I don't know anything
about their technique.
Wait a minute.
I've got it!
This technique is based
on a constellation!
Anyone looking at the sky
could figure that part out.
And the constellation is!
The Southern Cross!
Shit!
He both let it show on our faces!
He gave me a look like, seriously?
He just guessed my technique
was based on the Southern Cross,
but he wasn't sure about it!
Then I gave him that same stupid look!
I confirmed it for him!
If he figures out any more of my technique,
he'll be able to enter the monitor room.
I have to stop him here.
Back in a stalemate again.
But was it really the Southern Cross?
Tsumiki taught me that.
I don't really know about the other ones.
But isn't the Southern Cross
a four-star constellation?
Fushiguro!
Looks like I can still get close to Panda.
Panda, do you happen to know if the
Southern Cross has four stars in it?
Well, I mean it's a cross.
So there has to be at least four.
Kirara's technique must apply one of the
stars in the Southern Cross to each of us.
And I thought it might use that to
force us to maintain a certain distance.
But Kirara can approach the door.
And you and I can approach each other.
So maybe Kirara and the door's
stars are repelling ours.
Like opposite magnets
push each other away.
No, that doesn't sound right.
If that were true, Kyura would
just flee into the monitor room.
You're right.
And if they hugged the inside
of the door, we'd be stuck.
Hey, wait a minute.
What about this?
Star A is able to approach
Star B, but B can't approach A.
Each star has only one other
star they're compatible with,
and they cannot approach any other star but
that one, like in rock, paper, scissors.
But you and I can approach each other.
We have no problem moving
toward one another.
So that's a no.
Maybe it's more like a stamp rally.
Where you have to follow a set route
and approach each one in order.
And things with the same
star get drawn together.
That's interesting.
But what if the Sorcerer isn't counted
as one of the stars in the Constellation?
That can't be the case.
Because they were forced to
stay away from Demon Dog.
Just look at Kyurena.
They're obviously on high
alert about our next move.
because they're afraid that
while they're not looking,
we manage to get what we need in
order to enter that monitor room.
So forget four stars, there's
at least five or more. Right.
If my stamp rally theory is correct,
then with only four stars, we should
be able to approach Kirara freely.
But we can't, so there
has to be a fifth star.
And that's the star we have to pass
through to reach Kirara and that door.
What if there are six or seven stars?
Yeah, well, I'm really hoping
that's not what we're up against.
It's confusing enough with five
stars if they figured it out
I'm okay.
Don't worry about me.
Just go and find that star
Hey, don't go throwing cars right now!
The same of my star on you is on that car.
If you throw it, it'll just come back,
or pull you toward it
like Demon Dog did to me.
They probably have to touch the
target to plant a star on them.
No, they can't be right.
Kirara hasn't touched me or Rabbit Escape.
They only touched Demon Dog, Meaning
Kirara isn't tagging objects,
they're tagging cursed energy!
In order to tag doors and cars,
it might need someone to imbue cursed
energy into them ahead of time.
I knew it!
The car has residual cursed
energy from someone else.
If the technique doesn't
cover a wide range,
then traces of the other star should be…
There!
The fifth star!
I don't see any more residual cursed
energy from anyone other than us.
Kiraras already marked
their own cursed energy.
So they can't use it to
mark objects with the
same acroxed star that
they labeled me with.
Meaning they can't launch things
at me like they did with that car.
Once I touch that, I can approach Kirara.
Fushiguro's hypothesis was correct.
Kireira's cursed technique,
Love Rendezvous, assigns one of five stars
to the cursed energy of their targets,
using the Southern Cross as a base.
For one star to approach another, it
must follow a predetermined order.
Things marked with the same star
are attracted to each other.
Very impressive.
I can't believe you actually
figured out my technique.
Panda! Here, catch him!
That order was nearest
to the farthest star.
Constellations may look flat, but
they do, of course, have depth.
And each star has a different
distance from Earth.
You're so smart.
I bet you thought, there's no way I
could throw objects at you any longer.
Well, I can just lick the Ginon
star placed on my own cursed energy
and mark things with the same
A-Crux star that I put on you!
What?
How?
Where did it come from?
That boy, he never dismissed
his doggy Shikigami.
Did he figure out which of the same tagged
objects would be drawn to the other?
Then he put a wall between
himself and the Shikigami.
So the Shikigami would
be drawn into the wall.
Then he unleashed the doggie when
I was in a line between them.
Love rendezvous.
Cancel.
Please go out like the new mix?
Please, Kuroi, just hear us out.
Did you really do that?
Set me up with my own technique?
There's no way you could
have known if you or
the dog you would get
pulled toward the other.
I took a gamble, but
now I know for certain.
The one with the greater cursed
energy pulls the other towards it.
The first time I was
pulled into Demon Dog,
but when I strengthened my cursed energy
to guard against your incoming attack,
the opposite happened.
You're really just a first year?
You weren't cute at all, you know.
Please.
We don't have time.
Please hear us out.
All right, fine.
Itadori?
Fujikura... Panda...
Stay out of this.
Underestimating me, huh?
What is it with this kid?
He's not even trying to dodge my punches
You crazy or what?
This isn't like the fight, Shibuya
Yeah, this is me looking
Hakari in the eyes.
Until he accepts me,
I won't dodge anymore.
I won't fight back, not until he caves.
How's this?
I'll listen to what you have to say
for as long as you remain standing.
Kid, baby, stop.
These kids just want your help.
Just hear them out, OK?
I just said I would, didn't I?
Okay, Itadori, why me?
This is the first time we've met, right?
So why did you come to me?
It's because of your strength.
All my friends told me you were strong.
Of course, figures.
When one sorcerer asks another for help,
it's an understood agreement that
they're asking him to risk his life.
So if I'm gonna throw
my chips in with you,
you better show me that you have a
passion worth risking my life for?
right here and now.
Yet you offer me nothing, saying you're
just here following orders. What the hell?
Old man Yaga should be
weeding out losers like you.
I don't have any passion.
Huh?
I'm nothing but a cog.
A cog in a sorcerer's machine.
that keeps exercising curses.
A cog.
Wait, wait, wait.
Are you for real?
Cause that's damn boring.
Stop it!
Enough, Itadori!
It hurts, doesn't it?
You know what Gojo once told me?
That my cursed energy was coarser and
grittier than anyone else he's ever known.
Are you dead yet?
Hey, Panda! Who?
You and Sea Urchin Head!
Take Edori's body and get lost!
And don't ever come back!
He took three unguarded blows!
Plus I hit him with a whole
lot of punches before, too!
What the hell are you made of, kid?
I'm nothing but a cog.
But cogs have a function, you know.
My function is to keep exercising curses.
And because I need you to achieve that,
then I'll play along until you agree to it.
Kinji Hakari, what's your function?
This kid.
So this is what a cog's
passion looks like.
Fine.
I'll keep punching.
Kin, baby.
I can tell you're all heated up.
It's true.
The fever never lies.
Get down here, you three.
Let's cut a deal but you mean
it's resolved did you just
convince him to Do that mm-hmm
thank you for saving his life
All good we may hate the upper
brass at Jujutsu High but it's
undeniable kin's Fever burns
hottest when he's helping others
Please be advised
effective immediately a player has
added a new rule to the culling game.
Rule number nine, players will
know each other's information,
first names, last names,
number of points accumulated,
current colony and number of
rules added to the game by you.
You have gained five points for a kill.
You're damn right I killed him.
Not a single one of these
guys was strong enough.
It really was so much
better 400 years ago.
Where are you, Sukuna?
You have exceeded 200 points.
Would you like to consume 100 points
by adding a rule to the calling game?
Oh, right.
The rules.
If I knew their names and their
points telling me their strength.
Oh, but points go down when adding a rule.
So I'd need the number
of rules they added to.
And knowing which colony
they're in would be valuable.
Kogane, add a rule.
Reveal that information for every player.
I'll see you
next time.
You're in the space
between dreams and reality.
It's a curse.
How do you know my name?
I'm not like Itadori.
Once you step inside,
you too become a player.
And make them add a rule to let
Tsumiki escape the calling game.
You